Chhavi Jagotta Counselling Psychologist



Details: -

HNo. 586, Sector - 31, Gurgaon, Haryana, India. 122001

Contact number: - +91-9910277465 Email ID: - Chhavijagotta18@gmail.com

About me: -

I am a Counselling Psychologist with working experiences of 2 years now, open to providing counselling services for clients and experiencing new milestones with your organization. I am creative and sharp-minded with leadership and time-management skills and a work – ethic.

Language: -

English, Hindi and Punjabi

Skills: -

- Dedicated to ensuring the well-being of clients.
- Planning client-centric treatment plans.
- Communication skills.
- Time-management skills.
- Leadership and multitasking.

Marital status: -

Single

Work experience: -

Rocket Health, (Online) - Counselling Psychologist

August 2022 - Present

- Provided counselling services to a diverse population of clients.
- Developed individualised treatment plans to address a broad range of mental health concerns like anxiety, depression, phobias, and relationship concerns.
- Conducted support groups in the Discord community.
- Content creation (reels) for Instagram and YouTube.

Talk to Angel (Online) - Counselling Psychologist

August 2022 - Present

- Provided counselling services to a diverse population of clients.
- Developed individualised treatment plans to address a broad range of mental health concerns like anxiety, stress management, and personal growth.

Manastha, (Online) - Trainee, Counselling Psychologist

May 2021 - July 2021

- Provided counselling services to a diverse population of clients.
- Training 2 weeks program in building client rapport.

Education:-

M.Sc. in Clinical Psychology Amity University Haryana 2019 – 2021

B.A. in Applied Psychology Amity University Haryana 2016 – 2019

Class XIIth
D.A.V. Public School, Sector-14, Gurgaon
CBSE board, Completed 2016

Class Xth **D.A.V. Public School, Sector-14, Gurgaon**CBSE board, Completed 2014

Training and Internship experiences:-

- 1. One-month certification in 'How to take therapy session?' The PsyK- Life
- 2. Three-month certification in Trauma and Grief Therapy The PsyK Life

- 3. Overcoming overthinking The PsyK Life
- Three days online courses Rorschach Inkblot Test Fortis National Mental Health Program (July 2021)
- 5. One month internship in Clinical Psychology Fortis Memorial Research Institute (July 2021)
- **6.** Three-day online course in Sports Psychology **Fortis National Mental Health Program** (June 2021)
- 7. Three-day online course in Art Therapy Fortis National Mental Health Program (June 2021)
- 8. Three-day online course in Special Education Fortis National Mental Health Program (May 2021)
- One month Internship in Rehabilitation Psychology Psych-Vigyaan (May 2021)
- 10. One month Internship in Criminal Psychology Psych-Vigyaan (May 2020)
- 11. One month Internship in Clinical Psychology Manthan Clinic (December 2019)
- 12. One month internship in Clinical Psychology Fortis Memorial Research Institute (May 2019)
- 13. One month internship in Clinical Psychology Fortis Memorial Research Institute (May 2018)
- 14. Internship in Clinical Psychology Medanta The Medicity (May 2017)

Industrial Visits:

California Hypnosis Institute:

- Signature Analysis
- Handwriting Analysis
- Pendulum dowsing
- Chakra healing

Citizen Hospital, Gurugram:

- Developed observation skills.
- Gained knowledge about psychoeducation and therapy.
- Learning about case-history

Hobbies and Interests: - Painting, dancing, mandala art, playing badminton, cooking and baking cakes Salary expected: - Negotiable					